https://www.giantmicrobes.com/us/content/privacypolicy.html

1-877-MICROBE
My Cart (0 item)
white blood
Cells at Work!
crabs
Gonorrhea (Clap)
Mycoplasma
Syphilis (Pox)
Organs KLP 3-pack
Shop by Gift:
Website Privacy Policy
At Giantmicrobes, Inc. (hereinafter "Giantmicrobes") we take issues of privacy seriously. We want your experience shopping with us to be enjoyable and hassle free. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. We may change the terms from time to time and any change will be effective from the day of posting, so please check this page periodically.
SECURITY
We use all means at our disposal to safeguard the information you have provided using the latest technology Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us. Once we receive your information, we take appropriate steps that we believe are reasonable to protect the security of your data on our system, both internally and from outsiders, and to ensure the integrity of the data we collect. We use a combination of technological and policy methods to protect this data. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information. Please be aware that Giantmicrobes will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or e-mail.
WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED
We collect a limited amount of personal information from you in certain areas of the Giantmicrobes website (hereinafter the “Website”) for various reasons. The following is a description of what information is collected:
Personal Information. During the order process or when creating an account, we collect your name, address, phone number, email, credit card numbers and other personal information.
IP Addresses. An IP address is a number assigned to your computer when you connect to the Internet. As part of the protocol of the Internet, web servers can identify your computer by its IP address. In addition, web servers may be able to identify the type of browser and/or type of computer you are using. Giantmicrobes collects IP addresses and related information for the purposes of system administration, to assess the traffic to the Website and to maintain and improve the Website. We do not link IP addresses to your personally identifiable information. We can and will use IP addresses, however, to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our Website Terms and Conditions or to protect our service, the Website, customers or others.
Use of Cookies. Cookies are small bits of information that some websites (including the Website) transfer to an individual's hard drive for research purposes. Giantmicrobes uses cookies to analyze the traffic, such as total visitors and pages viewed on the Website, and make improvements based on the data we collect. Giantmicrobes never saves passwords or credit card information in cookies. The use of cookies has become a standard in the industry, especially at websites that provide any kind of personalized service. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can usually set your browser to refuse cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. If you refuse cookies, you may not be able to use some of the functionality of the Website. The Website’s advertisers and other partners may also use cookies in connection with the services and websites to which the Website links. We do not control these cookies.
WHO IS COLLECTING THIS INFORMATION
Giantmicrobes collects the information described above via the Website. In the case of third party features such as advertising, co-branded areas or links to other websites, such third parties may also collect information. You should review the applicable privacy policies of these third parties before providing personally identifiable information. Giantmicrobes is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.
HOW COLLECTED INFORMATION IS USED
In General. Giantmicrobes collects personal information for the purpose of processing and shipping orders. We may use the email address and contact information you've provided to send you updates about the status of any order you have placed. With your permission, we may also use the information to send you email or postal mail about special offers. At any time, you can choose that we not contact you by notifying us in writing at:
Giantmicrobes, Inc. 1 Dock Street Suite 615 Stamford, CT 06902 United States
Giantmicrobes also uses collected information to learn more about how visitors use the Website and to measure areas of interest. This allows Giantmicrobes to build features and functionality that will enhance your Website experience. We might also use this information to respond to e-mails, provide customer support, and enforce our Website Terms and Conditions or other similar matters. Aggregate information is also used to help us run and maintain the Website, study traffic patterns, and generally learn about the usage of the Website. While we do not currently sell individual information (email address and contact information) to outside companies for use in marketing, we reserve the right to do so in the future. Giantmicrobes is not responsible for any actions or policies of such outside companies. If you do not want your contact information passed on to other companies, simply write to us at the address above with the phrase "Take my name off the third party mailing list" in the subject line of the letter. We also reserve the right to license or sell aggregate information about the visitors to our website, but this information is not individually identifiable.
Unrelated Companies Working with Giantmicrobes. Giantmicrobes occasionally shares limited customer information with companies we hire to provide operational, marketing, or advertising support, companies that help us distribute our products and services, or companies that provide products and services we want to offer. Giantmicrobes is not responsible for any actions or policies of such companies. However, the companies we choose must satisfy our security and privacy requirements. We share your information with these companies only if they agree to treat it confidentially and only if it is legally permissible to do so. We limit the information we provide these companies to what we reasonably believe they "need to know" in connection with their agreement with Giantmicrobes and we don't permit them to use our customer information for any purposes outside our oversight or control.
Government Authorities and Litigation. Sometimes a law, court order, or other judicial or administrative process requires us to provide information to a government authority or party to a private lawsuit. We will provide the information that we in good faith believe is required to comply with the law, order, or other process. We may also have to disclose certain information in court documents if we have to bring an action against you, for example, to collect a debt you owe us.
USE OF FORUM
It is important to know that you may inadvertently provide personally identifiable information to third parties through your postings to a forum or participation in a chat session and we have no way to limit their use of the information you may provide. Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online (for example, in forums, message boards, or chat sessions) that information can be collected and used by people you don't know. While we strive to protect our user's personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you voluntarily disclose online and you do so at your own risk.
WITH WHOM THE INFORMATION MAY BE SHARED
Except as described above, we will not knowingly disclose or authorize the disclosure of personal identifiable information (other than aggregate statistical information) to any third party without your consent unless (1) we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may have breached our Website Terms and Conditions or who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Giantmicrobes' rights or property, other Website users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities, or (2) we believe in good faith that the law requires it.
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
While you are using the Website, you may be linked or directed to other third party websites outside the Website that are beyond Giantmicrobes’ control. Each of these third parties may have a privacy policy different from that of Giantmicrobes. Giantmicrobes is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties. You should review the applicable privacy policies of these third party websites before providing personally identifiable information.
QUESTIONS AND HOW TO CHANGE YOUR REGISTRATION INFORMATION
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or want to change, correct, update or delete your registration information, please contact Giantmicrobes at the following address or phone number and the necessary revisions will be made:
Giantmicrobes, Inc. 1 Dock Street Suite 615 Stamford, CT 06902 United States General Information: 1-(877)-MICROBE
This provision applies only to registration information collected via the Website.
Sign up today to learn about new GIANTmicrobes product releases, promotions and special discounts.
Submit
Please enter a valid email address.
Thank you for your subscription.
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
© 2002 - 2020
Giantmicrobes, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
Giantmicrobes, Inc., 78 Harvard Ave., Stamford, CT 06902 United States
Back to top
